Preliminary Guide to the Social Democrats, USA Records, 1937-1994 (Bulk 1970-1994)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Social Democrats, USA records 1937-1994 (Bulk 1970-1994)
Social Democrats, USA
101.9 linear feet Extent: 60,551 Items
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.01227
Language: English.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Social Democrats, USA Records was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1996 and 2001.
Biographical Note
Social Democrats, USA, is a descendant organization of the Socialist Pary of America.
Collection Overview
This collection (20,700 items, 35.5 linear feet, 1937-1984, bulk 1970-1984) includes office files and correspondence, and records from various organizations, such as the Young Social Democrats and the Youth Institute for Peace in the Middle East. Of note are some materials on prominent socialists, including Eugene Debs, Norman Thomas, and Carl Gershman. There are also important periodicals and special publications from 1937-1968 documenting American labor history, the Jim Crow Era, and civil rights issues in the 1960s. (96-104)
Addition (39,851 items, 66.4 linear feet, 1950-1994, bulk 1980-1994) includes correspondence with local chapters; organizational files on Young Social Democrats clubs, benefits, national conventions, fund raising, the yearly Eugene V. Debs Award dinners, and membership (including membership cards); subject files on people (including Bayard Rustin), other leftist organizations (especially Socialist International), labor unions, and countries and regions (including South Africa, Poland, Spain, the Soviet Union, and Latin America); and publications and newspapers related to socialism. Material also includes 108 electronic computer files that have been migrated to the Special Collections server; 2 cloth banners and 3 plaques/awards; 351 black-and-white photographs; 8 color prints; 4 videocassettes; 243 audio cassette tapes; 2 digital audio tapes; and 4 phonograph records. (01-0079)
Subject Headings
Debs, Eugene V. (Eugene Victor), 1855-1926; Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968; Gershman, Carl; Rustin, Bayard, 1912-1987; Social Democrats, U.S.A.; Youth Institute for Peace in the Middle East; Young Social Democrats (U.S.); Socialist International; African Americans -- Civil rights -- History -- 20th century; African Americans -- History -- 1877-1964; African Americans -- Social conditions; Labor -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions; Labor unions -- United States; Socialism -- South Africa; Socialism -- Poland; Socialism -- Spain; Socialism -- Soviet Union; Socialism -- Latin America; Journalism, Socialist; United States -- Race relations; Machine-readable records; Black-and-white photographs; Color photographs; Videocassettes; Audiocassettes; Banners; Plaques; Phonograph records; Sound recordings
Contents of Collection
- Accession 96-104
  - Socialist Party National Committee Files, 1971-1974;Debs Award Dinner Files -- 1980, 1981. (Box 1)
  - Lane Kirkland Dinner Receipt Book and Files; Debs Dinners -- 1976, 1977, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Young Social Democrats (YSD) Office Files, Convention Files -- 1978, 1980,1982;YSD National Convention -- 1979; Young People's Socialist League (YSPL) Correspondence, Office Files, Conventions Files; Conventions Files (AFLCIO, Socialist Internat'l. - Portugal, 1983, etc.). (Box 3)
  - YSD Office Files; College Democrats of America Files. (Box 4)
  - YSD Correspondence; YSD University and College Files; YSD Publications; YSD National Action Committee Minutes. (Box 5)
  - Social Democrats National Conventions -- 1974, 1976;Office Files; Socialist Party Central American Conference -- 1983. (Box 6)
  - Social Democrats (SD) Office Files; National Conference Files -- 1974, 1976;Financial Papers; National Committee Files -- 1977-78. (Box 7)
  - SD Office Files; Organizations Files (Labor Party, Labor unions, etc.); Events Files (Solidarity Day, Moscow Olympics, etc.). (Box 8)
  - SD National Committee -- 1975, 1979;Debs Dinners -- 1977,1978. (Box 9)
  - Debs Dinners -- 1973-1979. (Box 10)
  - Debs Dinner -- 1979;Muravchik Luncheon; Convention Files -- 1972. (Box 11)
  - SD National Convention Files -- 1972, 1973, 1982. (Box 12)
  - SD National Convention Files -- 1982;National Committee Files -- 1980-1983;Debs Dinner -- 1983;Socialist International Middle East Roundtable Conference -- Vienna, 1978;various other social functions files. (Box 13)
  - SD Office Files; National Committee -- 1973, 1974, 1983;Press Releases -- 1970; Carl Gershman Writings and Correspondence; Guestbooks; Sheinkman-J.P. Stevens Dinner; National Convention Files; Printed Material ( New America). (Box 14)
  - Hess Boycott -- 1984; Youth Institute for Peace in the Middle East (YIPME) Files; International Files (France and Germany only); Various Items marked To be filed. (Box 15)
  - YIPME Files -- 1975-79, 1984, 1993;Other Youth Programs Files. (Box 16)
  - Young Social Democrats Files -- 1993, 1994;Other Youth Programs Files; Office Files; Jewish Labor Committee; International Files by country (Australia- Cameroon). (Box 17)
  - SD National Convention -- 1970, 1972;International Files by country (Balitc, Basle, Barbados); Policy and Committee Files. (Box 18)
  - SD National Convention -- 1978, 1980;National Action Committee -- 1984, 1986-1988. (Box 19)
  - SD National Action Committee -- 1974-1984;Office Files. (Box 20)
  - National Committee -- 1983-1986, 1989-1990;International Files by country (Great Britain through Italy). (Box 21)
  - International Files (China through Estonia); Office Files -- early 1970s;States Membership Correspondence (Ala. through Ca.). (Box 22)
  - Pamphlets; Estates/bequests Files; Office Files; Bound Articles of Incorporation. (Box 23)
  - Oversize
    - Norman Thomas materials (including diplomas) (Box 1)
    - Eugene Debs Portrait (Box 1)
    - Social Democratic Federation of NY Charter (Box 1)
    - Photographs. (Box 1)
    - Periodicals: Urban Review, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Photo History, Labor's Challenge, 1937 (Box 1)
    - New America layout boards. (Box 1)
  - Printed Materials
    - Periodicals: Role of the Party in the Fight for Socialism, ca. 1949; Negro Worker, 1937; Labor Action, 1957-8; Negro in Politics, 1948; Bulletin of the Workers Party, 1949; The Negro: His Future in America, 1943; Race, Rage, and Eldridge Cleaver, 1968; Socialist Songbook, 1959. (Box 1)
- Accession 2001-0079
  - contents of Box 1: (Box 1)
    Reformat newspaper clippings and coated paper; remove rusty fasteners; resleeve photographs.
    - Local publications and correspondence
      - Los Angeles Local, 1976, (two folders) (Box 1)
      - Maryland Local (Box 1)
      - Correspondence with Locals, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
      - Austin Local (Box 1)
      - Boston Local (Box 1)
      - Buffalo Local (Box 1)
      - Connecticut Local (Box 1)
      - Detroit Local (Box 1)
      - Louisiana Local (Box 1)
      - Indiana Local, (two folders) (Box 1)
      - Los Angeles Local, 1975, (three folders) (Box 1)
        [resleeve photographs]
      - Maryland Local (Box 1)
      - Miami Local, (two folders) (Box 1)
      - Minnesota SD Local (Box 1)
      - Miss., Missouri, Mont., Neb. M-A-L Correspondence (Box 1)
      - Nassau Local (Box 1)
      - LNY, (two folders) (Box 1)
      - New York Local, 1975, (four folders) (Box 1)
      - New York Local through 1974, (three folders) (Box 1)
      - Sacramento Local (Box 1)
      - New York Local Newsletter (Box 1)
      - Philadelphia Local, (three folders) (Box 1)
      - Pittsburgh Local (Box 1)
    - Vanni Montana (Box 1)
    - Sam Shube (Box 1)
    - Germany: Fiedrich Ebert Stiftung (Box 1)
    - Housing March, Washington, D.C. 1989 October 7 (Box 1)
    - A. Philip Randolph Institute (APRI) 1993, (three folders) (Box 1)
    - Songs, Skits and Plays
      - Benefit Songs 1975 (Box 1)
      - YPSL play 1974, (two folders) (Box 1)
      - Skit sheet music 1974 (Box 1)
      - Script and songs, 1974 Benefit (Box 1)
      - 1972-1976 YPSL Skits, (two folders) (Box 1)
  - contents of Box 2: (Box 2)
    Remove rusty fasteners; reformat newspaper clippings and coated paper.
    - Songs, skits and plays, continued
      - YPSL Skits, continued 1983, 1984, 1985, (two folders) (Box 2)
    - YIPME Flyer Series, Puede este hombre traer la paz al Medio Oriente (Box 2)
    - YPSL Benefit 1975 (Box 2)
    - YPSL Benefit 1975 [oversize items removed to legal-sized box 30] (Box 2)
    - 1982 Benefit Journal Copy (Box 2)
    - Convention (Box 2)
    - 1987 YSD Convention (Box 2)
    - Randolph, A. Philip, 1980, (two folders) (Box 2)
    - Reebok Human Rights Award (Box 2)
    - Racism (Box 2)
    - Rassabach, Eisa, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
    - Christopher Raver (Box 2)
    - A. Philip Randolph Institute, through 1979, (two folders) (Box 2)
    - Radical publications, (two folders) (Box 2)
    - Radical movements 1978, (two folders) (Box 2)
    - Helen Dwight Reid Educational Foundation (Box 2)
    - For the Record (Box 2)
    - Reedy, George 1993 (Box 2)
    - Pioneer Valley Social Democrats, USA, (two folders) (Box 2)
    - Radical Movements, 1975-1977, (two folders) (Box 2)
    - Presidential Election, 1992, (three folders) (Box 2)
    - Presidential Elections, file 2, (three folders) (Box 2)
    - Presidential Elections, file 2 [oversize items removed to legal-sized box 30] (Box 2)
    - Presidential Elections--Democrats, 1992 (Box 2)
    - Presidential Election, 1992 Election Mailings (Box 2)
    - A. Philip Randolph Institute, (three folders) (Box 2)
    - A. Philip Randolph Institute, (five folders) (Box 2)
  - contents of Box 3: (Box 3)
    Remove rusty fasteners; reformat newsprint and coated fax paper; be aware of sensitive information.
    - Radosh,Ron, (two folders) (Box 3)
    - Porter, Paul, (four folders) (Box 3)
    - Polytechnic University 1993 (Box 3)
    - From Popularism to Bolchevikism: Chapter I (UFT educational unit) (Box 3)
    - Norman Podhoretz (Box 3)
    - Political affaires (Box 3)
    - Antonio Ybarra-Rojas (Box 3)
      Be aware of sensitive information
    - Bayard Rustin's 75th Birthday Celebration (Box 3)
    - Roche, John (Box 3)
    - YDS Files (Box 3)
    - Request for Info. (Box 3)
    - USYC, (two folders) (Box 3)
    - Phelps Dodge (Box 3)
    - NEC-YSD (Box 3)
    - International Youth Year
      - IYY (Box 3)
      - IYY, Jamaica Conference (Box 3)
      - International Youth Conference, Jamaica 1985, (four folders) (Box 3)
    - SDUSA (Box 3)
    - Press, articles about SD (Box 3)
    - New Members, (two folders) (Box 3)
    - Membership list (Box 3)
    - YSD Membership list (Box 3)
    - International Youth Conference, Moscow (Box 3)
    - Sectarian Left Groups
      - Sectarian Left Groups: All Peoples Congress (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: International Correspondence (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: International Socialist Organization (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: INCAR (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: New Allisnce Party (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: New Union Party (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: Revolutionary International Movement (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: Revolutionary Socialist League (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: Socialist Labor Party (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: Socialist Workers Party (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: Spartacus League (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: Workers World Party (Box 3)
      - Sectarian Left Groups: Workers League (Box 3)
    - South Africa Project, (four folders) (Box 3)
    - YIPME, (four folders) (Box 3)
    - Murauchik Dinner 1977 (Box 3)
    - George Washington University (Box 3)
  - contents of Box 4: (Box 4)
    Reformat newsprint and coated fax paper.
    - Spain 1993 (Box 4)
    - Spain (Box 4)
    - Spain--File 2, (three folders) (Box 4)
    - Spain--File 3, (three folders) (Box 4)
    - Spain--File 4, (two folders) (Box 4)
    - Spain--File 5 (Box 4)
    - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU) (Box 4)
    - The World According to Andrew Young by C. Gershman (Box 4)
    - Jerry Wurf (Box 4)
    - Wytwyoky, Bohdan (Box 4)
    - Workers Party 1993 (Box 4)
    - Workers Revolutionary Party (Box 4)
    - Jim Wood (Box 4)
    - Workers Defense League (Box 4)
    - World without War Council, Inc., (two folders) (Box 4)
    - Wilson, William Julius 1992-1993 (Box 4)
    - Winograd, Morley 1993 (Box 4)
    - Witness for Peace (Box 4)
    - Wlodarczyk, Waldemar J. (Box 4)
    - Lynn R. Williams (Box 4)
    - Why America Needs a Social Democratic Movement (Box 4)
    - William Winpisinger (Box 4)
    - Worker Rights 1993 (Box 4)
    - Steve Weiner (Box 4)
    - Rose Weinrib (Box 4)
    - Welfare Reform (Box 4)
    - West, Cornell, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Workplace Democracy 1993 (Box 4)
    - Ron Wegsman (Box 4)
    - US Youth Council, (four folders) (Box 4)
    - John Warnock (State Department), (three folders) (Box 4)
    - US Youth Council, (three folders) (Box 4)
    - United Federation of Teachers (Box 4)
    - David Twersky (Box 4)
    - Doan Van Toai, (two folders) (Box 4)
  - contents of Box 5: (Box 5)
    Reformat newspaper clippings and coated fax paper.
    - United Steelworkers of America, (two folders) (Box 5)
    - Toai Charnoff Book Reception (Box 5)
    - Village Voice (Box 5)
    - Vorndran, Kurt (Box 5)
    - Jewish Socialist Verband (Box 5)
    - Voters Registration, (two folders) (Box 5)
    - USYC Labor Desk (Box 5)
    - UFT Lecture Series (Box 5)
    - November 1987 Trade Union Meetings (Box 5)
    - October 1987 Trade Union Meetings (Box 5)
    - Todorvich, Miro M. (Box 5)
    - Trier Colloquium on Socialism and Freedom, 1977 May 4 (Box 5)
    - Ben Wattenberg (Box 5)
    - Mark Weber (Box 5)
    - Does America Need a Social Democratic Movement?--Transcripts (Box 5)
    - War Resisters League, (seven folders) (Box 5)
    - Trotskyists (Box 5)
    - Tufts University, The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy (Box 5)
    - Gus Tyler (Box 5)
    - Stajka, Sandra (Box 5)
    - Starr, Paul (Box 5)
    - United Steelworkers of America (Box 5)
    - Erwin Suall (Box 5)
    - Sumoff, Barnett Dr. (Box 5)
    - Economic Convention (Box 5)
    - Education Series, 1994-1995 (Box 5)
    - Embassador Luigi Einaudi (Box 5)
    - Eisenbach, Elliot (Box 5)
    - El Salvador Luncheon, 1992 March 29,Freedom House (Box 5)
      Remove materials from envelopes.
    - Election Campaign 1980, Carter vs. Reagan (Box 5)
    - 1984 Elections, (two folders) (Box 5)
    - Elections 1992-1994 (Box 5)
    - 1980 Elections (Box 5)
    - International Union of Electrical Workers (Box 5)
    - Stuart Elliott (Box 5)
    - Elliott- Toth (Box 5)
    - El Salvador-MNR (Box 5)
    - Endorsement Statements / Responses (Box 5)
    - Farah Boycott (Box 5)
    - East-West Technology Transfers, (three folders) (Box 5)
    - Evelyn Dubrow (Box 5)
    - Local 1199 of the Drug, Hospital and Care Employee Union (Box 5)
    - Equality: Voice of Democratic Socialism (Box 5)
    - Ethnics: A New Separatism, by Bayard Rustin ( 1974; AFL-CIO Federationists) (Box 5)
  - contents of Box 6: (Box 6)
    - Students for Solidarity (Box 6)
    - Mauricio Membreão-Gaitãn (Box 6)
    - Homework Ban (Box 6)
    - International Contacts (Box 6)
    - YSD 1993 (Box 6)
    - 1989Retreat (Box 6)
    - Nicaragua (Box 6)
    - Nicaragua Debate (Box 6)
    - Frontlash, (three folders) (Box 6)
    - YSD International Affairs Committee, 1986 (Box 6)
    - Viewpoint, IUD (Box 6)
    - Washington Local (Box 6)
    - SPS (Box 6)
    - USYC Trip Reports (Box 6)
    - NEC-YSD (Box 6)
    - T-shirt Design (Box 6)
    - Young Democratic Clubs of America (Box 6)
    - USSA/NSA (Box 6)
    - SD-NC-NAC (Box 6)
    - Graphics (Box 6)
    - Industrial Policy Statement (Box 6)
    - Midwest Organizing Trip (Box 6)
    - Midwest Conference (Box 6)
    - YSD Bulletin March 1985 (Box 6)
    - Socialism (Box 6)
    - Youth Coalitions for Democracy (Box 6)
    - Kemble Paper Democrat Party (Box 6)
    - Freedom House (Box 6)
    - Freedom Federation (Box 6)
    - Foreign Policy Asociation (Box 6)
    - Films (Box 6)
    - Feldman, Sandra (Box 6)
    - Paul Feldman (Box 6)
    - Farrakhan (Box 6)
    - Farm Labor Organizing Committee (Box 6)
    - New America (Box 6)
    - Randolph, A. Philip (Box 6)
    - New America (serial) 1972 July-1980 August (Box 6)
  - contents of Box 7: (Box 7)
    Reformat newsprint and coated fax paper
    - Dues Billing (Box 7)
    - James T. Farrell, (four folders) (Box 7)
    - Bogdan Denitch (Box 7)
    - Detente and the Left after Afghanistan, Gershman- Harrington Debate (Box 7)
    - Dissent (Box 7)
    - Coalition for a Democratic Majority (Box 7)
    - Doctors without Frontiers Trip, (two folders) (Box 7)
    - Doctors without Borders, (two folders) (Box 7)
    - M. Stanton Evans Debate, Georgetown, 1979 April 5 (Box 7)
    - Expanding Economic Democracy (Box 7)
    - DSOC File 2, (two folders) (Box 7)
    - Democratic Socialism Federation (Box 7)
    - David Evanier (Box 7)
    - Energy (Box 7)
    - Engstrom, Herb (Box 7)
    - Epstein, Alec (Box 7)
    - Equality: Voice of Democratic Socialism (Box 7)
    - Democratic Platform Hearings, 1984 (Box 7)
    - Proposition A, California ( 1984) (Box 7)
    - Democratic Socialist of America-file 2, (three folders) (Box 7)
    - Progressive Alliance (Box 7)
    - Prospective Quarterly Publication, Possible Supplement to Notes (Box 7)
    - Grants (removed to legal-sized box) (Box 7)
    - Paddington, Arch (Box 7)
    - Proposal (Box 7)
    - Grant Proposal (Box 7)
    - Publications (Box 7)
    - 1984 Presidential Candidates (Box 7)
    - Presidential Elections 1980 (Box 7)
    - Puebla Institute (Box 7)
    - Presidential Election 1988 (Box 7)
    - Presidential Endorsement of 1988 (Box 7)
    - Human Rights (Box 7)
    - Human Rights Conference, (two folders) (Box 7)
  - contents of Box 8: (Box 8)
    - Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) (Box 8)
    - Feldman, Paul (Box 8)
    - Sol Feinstone (Box 8)
    - Fund for an Open Society (Box 8)
    - Walter Galenson (Box 8)
    - The Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 8)
    - Financial Matters (Box 8)
    - Finances / Pledges (Box 8)
    - Sam Fishman (Box 8)
    - Fletcher Social Democrats (Box 8)
    - Jane Fonda (Box 8)
    - Freedman, Rita, Letters to the Editor (Box 8)
    - Joel Freedman (Box 8)
    - Rita Freedman Biography (Box 8)
    - Freedman (Box 8)
    - Freedom Federation (Box 8)
    - Freedman's Writings, (three folders) (Box 8)
    - Freedom House, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
    - Freedom House, through 1981 (Box 8)
    - Freedom House, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - Freedom Medicine (Box 8)
    - Freedom House, 1992-1993, (two folders) (Box 8)
    - Freedom House, 1993, (two folders) (Box 8)
    - El Salvador, Freedom House Project, (two folders) (Box 8)
    - Free Trade Agreement--File 2, 1991-1993 (Box 8)
    - Samuel H. Friedman (Box 8)
    - Foreign Policy Research Institute (Box 8)
    - Foundation for Democratic Education, Inc. FDE (Box 8)
    - Friedrich Ebert Foundation (Box 8)
    - Frisancho, Roberto Javier, 1993 (Box 8)
    - [Frontlash], (two folders) (Box 8)
    - Frontlash, 1970-1974, (three folders) (Box 8)
    - Frontlash, 1975-1979, (three folders) (Box 8)
    - Frontlash, 1980, (three folders) (Box 8)
  - contents of Box 9: (Box 9)
    - Fund Raising SDUSA (Box 9)
    - Fund Appeal of Fall 1988 (Box 9)
    - Fund Appeals, through 1981 (Box 9)
    - Forward, Jewish Daily (Box 9)
    - Sandra Feldman (Box 9)
    - Cure Right (Box 9)
    - Curtin, George (Box 9)
    - 1995 Debs Dinner, Morton Bahr, Speeches, (two folders) (Box 9)
    - 1995 Debs Dinner, Morton Bahr, Panel (Box 9)
    - SD, Credo, 1991-1992, [removed to legal-sized box 30] (Box 9)
    - Eric Chenoweth (Box 9)
    - Ramsey Clarke (Box 9)
    - CCISPES (Box 9)
    - CID Cuba Independiente y Democrática (Box 9)
    - Corporate Takeovers, Summer 1989 (Box 9)
    - National Labor Caucus (Box 9)
    - National Endowment for Democracy, 1993, (two folders) (Box 9)
    - The Resource Center, (two folders) (Box 9)
    - Organizational List Mailing, Credo Papers, File 1, Dialog I, (two folders) (Box 9)
    - China, Social Democrats (Box 9)
    - Muravchik Paper (Box 9)
    - NAM (Box 9)
    - National Education Association, NEA (Box 9)
    - National Democratic Institute of International Affairs, (two folders) (Box 9)
    - Moscow Olympics Protest (Box 9)
    - Max Mont (Box 9)
    - Eusebio M. Mujal-León (Box 9)
    - Joshua Muravchick (Box 9)
    - Emanuel Muravchik (Box 9)
  - contents of Box 10: (Box 10)
    - Credo Seminars / #1 Papal Encyclical 1997 March 27 (Box 10)
    - Association for Union Democracy (Box 10)
    - Attacks on Social Democrats, (two folders) (Box 10)
    - Atran Foundation (Box 10)
    - Seth Balin (Box 10)
    - Gregory Bardacke (Box 10)
    - Conservative Foundations (Box 10)
    - Communist Party (Box 10)
    - Communist Workers Party (Box 10)
    - Committee in Support of Solidarity, (four folders) (Box 10)
    - Penn Kemble (Box 10)
    - Kemble Re: Economic Policy Commission, 1977 January 2 (Box 10)
    - Eugenia Kemble (Box 10)
    - Karatnysky, Adrian, (two folders) (Box 10)
    - Kemble, Program Revisions, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Michael Kerper, European Year (Box 10)
    - Michael Kerper (Box 10)
    - Ralph Kessler (Box 10)
    - Key List Mailings (Box 10)
    - Jim Burnett (Box 10)
    - Dennis King (Box 10)
    - Kolakowski, Leszek (Box 10)
    - June Kopilow (Box 10)
    - Seymour Kopilow (Box 10)
    - Kubiske, Daniel (Box 10)
    - Kugler, Israel (Box 10)
    - National YSD (Box 10)
    - YSD Constitutions (Box 10)
    - Youth Memo (Box 10)
    - Young European Left (Box 10)
    - YSD Conference 1994 August 5-1994 August 6 (Box 10)
    - Stephen Young (Box 10)
    - Labor Movement General, (two folders) (Box 10)
    - Labor Committee on Caribbean and Central America, (two folders) (Box 10)
    - Tom Kahn, (four folders) (Box 10)
    - Labor Movement, Left Activity, (three folders) (Box 10)
  - contents of Box 11: (Box 11)
    - 1992 Debs Dinner, Michael Sacco
      - Correspondence/General (Box 11)
      - Sponsors (Box 11)
      - Finances (Box 11)
      - List not on Disks (Box 11)
      - Publicity (Box 11)
      - Speeches (Box 11)
      - Hotel / Party (Box 11)
      - Ticket Sales (Box 11)
      - Printed Material, (two folders) (Box 11)
    - 1993 Debs Dinner, Moe Biller
      - Printed Material, (two folders); (1 black and white print) (Box 11)
    - 1991 Debs Dinner, Robert Georgine
      - Lists not on disks (Box 11)
      - Publicity (Box 11)
      - Ticket Sales (Box 11)
      - Greetings (Box 11)
      - Hotel / Party (Box 11)
      - Printed Material (Box 11)
      - Correspondence / General (Box 11)
      - Finances (Box 11)
      - Sponsors (Box 11)
      - Speeches (Box 11)
    - 1990 Debs Dinner, Al Shanker
      - Sponsors (Box 11)
      - Seating (Box 11)
      - Publicity (Box 11)
      - Greetings (Box 11)
      - Correspondence / General (Box 11)
      - Hotel / Party (Box 11)
      - Lists not on disk (Box 11)
      - Finances (Box 11)
      - Ticket Sales (Box 11)
      - Speeches (Box 11)
      - Printed Material (Box 11)
    - 1989 Debs Dinner, John Sweeny
      - Dais (Box 11)
      - Lists not on disk. (Box 11)
      - Correspondence / General (Box 11)
      - Finances (Box 11)
      - Speeches (Box 11)
      - Greetings (Box 11)